{"data":[{"question":"Bangkok is ________ capital of Thailand.","a":"a","b":"one","c":"the","d":"an","answer":"3","explain":"\n- We use the when there is only one of something","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"17","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"1"},{"question":"Are you free ________ Saturday?","a":"on","b":"at","c":"in","d":"into","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Prepositions of time: at, in, on: \n+ In: for seasons, months, years, centuries, long periods.\u00a0\n+ At: for a precise time (at 3 o'clock, at noon, at sunrise, at the moment).\u00a0\n+ On: for specific day and dates (on Sunday, on 6 March, on Christmas Day, on my birthday...).\u00a0","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"17","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"1"},{"question":"There are ________ girls in our class.","a":"no","b":"not","c":"none","d":"none of","answer":"1","explain":"- We use no as a determiner before nouns: means not any","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"17","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"1"},{"question":"Let ________ go for a walk.","a":"we","b":"us","c":"you","d":"our","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Let us = We: used when you suggest that you and other people do something","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"17","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"1"},{"question":"What is your name? ________ name is Linda.","a":"Your","b":"His","c":"My","d":"Her","answer":"3","explain":"\n- Your name (question)- my name.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"17","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"1"},{"question":"What's ________ name? His name is Henry.","a":"his","b":"her","c":"your","d":"my","answer":"1","explain":"\n- His name (answer)- his name.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"17","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"1"},{"question":"I'm a pupil. I'm a ________, too.","a":"teacher","b":"pupil","c":"student","d":"doctor","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Too: used at the end of a sentence or clause to mean 'also'- they're both pupils.\u00a0","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"17","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"1"},{"question":"Is this your pencil? No, it isn't. It is ________ pencil.","a":"his","b":"my","c":"your","d":"hers","answer":"1","explain":"\n- My, your and hers are incorrect","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"17","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"1"},{"question":"Are these your coats? Yes they are ________.","a":"their coats","b":"ours","c":"our coats","d":"yours","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Ours (possessive determiner): means our coats","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"17","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"1"},{"question":"Are your free ________ Friday evening?","a":"in","b":"at","c":"on","d":"from","answer":"3","explain":"- We use on for days","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"17","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"1"}]}